

Mustafa Naiby

A Professional Web & Graphic Designer

CONTACTME

Phone Number:

+93764131287

Email:

mustafanaiby111@gmail.com

Website:

mustafajhon.github.io

Address:

Nili, Daykundi, Afghanistan

SKILLS

нтиг

CSS

Java Script

Python

photoshop

React Is

INTERESTS

Travelind

Creating

Running

Photography

Book Reading

PROFILE

Reliable, qualified, and experienced graphic designer working mainly in the IT industry, particularly in software houses. Excellence in creativity, problem-solving, time-management, and technical skills. Offering industrial exposure and providing design solutions for a broad range of webmasters and app developers. Works well with the team of graphic designers, and highly participative in business meetings.

EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer (2013 - 2015)

I Led a team that focused on providing designs to e-commerce websites. Completed most orders in a 6-month period and won the perfect designer award.

Web Designer (2018 - Now)

I worked on testing and improving their websites' designs. Worked with different content management systems and prepared plans for website structure and design.

English Teacher (2016 - 2018)

I thought English for nearly two year in Watan All Around Course, and also thought some programming languages like python and java.

EDUCATION

Information Technology (2018 - 2020)

I have an Associates degree in Information Technology that I studied in Afghan Institute of Technology(AIT).

Bachelors in Computer Science (2017 - 2021)

I have a bachelor of Computer Science from kabul University. and I have e participated in many web projects. with full confidence I can say that I have full hands on building web pages.